Guide to the Office of the Dean, Washington Square College and Washington Square and University College of Arts and Science 1929-1984 (Bulk 1951-1980) RG.19
New York University Archives
- Series I: Washington Square Dean's Files, 168422
  - Subseries D: Administrative Subject Files, 168423
    - Financial: Development: General File, 1970-1971; 168647 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Financial: Development: General File, 1971-1972; 168646 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Financial: Development: General File, 1972-1974; 168645 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Financial: Development, Office for, 1963-1978; 168644 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Financial: Development, Office for: Arts and Sciences, 1978; 168643 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Edward H. Innet, 1972-1973; 168642 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Financial: Effective Use of Resources, Commission on the, 1968-1970; 168641 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Financial: Esso Education Foundation, 1972; 168640 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Financial: Foundation Giving, 1968-1969; 168639 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Financial: Foundation Summaries, 1975-1976; 168638 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Financial: Gottesman Foundation, 1971-1977; 168637 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Financial: Graduate Record Exam, 1972-1973; 168636 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226000 3
    - Financial: Housing, Departmental Budget for, 1978; 168635 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Post Seconddary Research Fund, 1975-1976; 168634 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Financial: Japanese Studies at NYU, Fund Raising for, 1973; 168633 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Financial: Jean R. Fitzhugh, 1972; 168632 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Financial: Louis Calder Foundation, 1972-1973; 168631 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Financial: Mabel Rabkin Fund Raising Steering Committee, 1971; 168630 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Financial: Mail Complaints, 1968-1973; 168629 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      bar code #: 3 1142 042260003
    - Financial: Maitland Lecture, 1959-1967; 168628 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Mellon Foundation Professorships, 1972; 168627 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Financial: Morgan Guaranty Trust, 1972; 168626 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Financial: Nader, Ralph, 1975; 168625 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Financial: NEH, 1966-1975; 168624 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Financial: NEH: Faculty Grants, 1970; 168623 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Financial: NEH: Visual Arts Program, 1975; 168622 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Financial: Netzer Committee Fiscal Review, 1975; 168621 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Financial: Oliva Commission, 1971; 168620 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Pre-Med Fellowships, 1973; 168619 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      bar code #:3 1142 04226000 3
    - Financial: Receptions, Departmental Funding for, 1978-1979; 168618 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Financial: Ryan, Marjorie Langley: Estate of, 1973; 168617 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Financial: School Revenues, Expenses, and Capital Expenditures, 1976; 168616 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Financial: Security Officer Contracts, 1968; 168615 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Financial: Stewart Mott Scholarship for Political Leadership, 1976; 168614 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Financial: Student Center Reservations, 1967-1968; 168613 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Financial: Student Lounges, 1964-1974; 168612 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Sunrise Semester: Correspondence File, 1971-1977; 168611 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226001 1
    - Sunrise Semester: Educational Policy Committee, 1958-1977; 168610 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Sunrise Semester: Examinations, 1972; 168609 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Sunrise Semseter: Fan Mail, 1971-1977; 168608 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Sunrise Semester: Fund Raising, 1971-1977; 168607 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Sunrise Semester: Hearst Foundation, 1972-1977; 168606 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Sunrise Semester: National Endowment for the Humanities, 1973-1975; 168605 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Sunrise Semester: Proposals, 1976; 168604 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Sunrise Semester: Publicity, 1972-1977; 168603 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Advisement, 1963-1974; 168602 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226002 9
    - Advisement: Background for Reference, 1961-1962; 168601 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Advisement: Student Correspondence, 1973-1977; 168600 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Advisory Committee Subcommittees, 1943-1975; 168599 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Advisory Council on Continuing Education, undated; 168598 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Affirmative Action, Office of, 1971-1973; 168597 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Affirmative Action, Office of, 1974-1975; 168596 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Air Conditioning, 1959-1970; 168595 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Album, 1964-1967; 168594 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Alpha Fraternities, 1952-1966; 168593 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Alternate Education Program, 1973-1974; 168592 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - American Academy of Dramatic Arts, 1958-1959; 168591 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - American Architectural Experience, 1975-1976; 168590 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - American Association of Higher Education, 1971-1973; 168589 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - American Committee for Émigré Scholars, 1960-1964; 168588 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - American Conference of Academic Deans, 1968-1975; 168587 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1961-1968; 168586 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226003 7
    - American Language Institute, 1964-1973; 168585 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - American Psychological Association, 1963; 168584 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - American Research Institute in Turkey, 1969-1974; 168583 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - American Sociological Society, 1961-1962; 168582 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - American Universities Field Staff, 1964-1965; 168581 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - American University in Cairo, 1970-1974; 168580 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Antopol, William, 1969-1972; 168579 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Apex Project, 1966; 168578 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Applied Social Research, Center for, 1959; 168577 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - A etice (Literary Magazine), 1961; 168576 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Area Distribution Requirements, 1969-1970; 168575 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Army Education Centers 1965, 168574 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Arnold Library, 1966-1970; 168573 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Art Competition, 1961-1965; 168572 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Arts and Science Administration, 1963-1964; 168571 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Arts and Science Research Fund, 1960-1972; 168570 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Arts and Sciences (Magazine), 1961-1967; 168569 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Arts in Higher Education (Carnegie Commission), 1972; 168568 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Arts, School of the, 1965; 168567 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Arts, School of the, 1966-1975; 168566 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Aspira College Retention Freshman Counseling Program, undated; 168565 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Assistant Teacher Program, 1967; 168564 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1964-1976; 168563 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226004 5
    - Association of American Universities, 1968; 168562 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Astronomy, 1963; 168561 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Athletics, 1961-1967; 168560 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Auditing, 1964-1969; 168559 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Average Computing, 1974; 168558 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Baccalaureate Service, 1967-1969; 168557 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Bachelor of Literature, 1964; 168556 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Barron's NYU Profile, 1971; 168555 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Bellevue, 1961-1968; 168554 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Benchmark Evaluation Committee, 1976; 168553 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Bennett, Jr., Dr. Ivan L., 1970; 168552 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Berezin, Irving, 1968-1972; 168551 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Berg Chair, 1967-1968; 168550 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Berger, Dean, 1969-1972; 168549 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Bernsten, Howard, 1966-1973; 168548 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Bicentennial Celebration--US, 1971-1974; 168547 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Bilingual Education, 1974-1975; 168546 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Biography, Post Doctoral Seminar, 1963-1966; 168545 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Black Experience, Courses on, 1968-1976; 168544 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Black Student's Association, 1968-1970; 168543 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Black Studies, 1969-1970; 168542 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Black Studies Degree Program, 1969-1972; 168541 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Blind Students, 1964-1974; 168540 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Blue Key National Honour Fraternity, 1967-1968; 168539 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Bonus Courses, 1962-1963; 168538 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Bookman Fund, 1963-1967; 168537 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - British Summer Schools, 1967-1968; 168536 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226005 2
    - Brittany, The, 1969-1976; 168535 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Bromberg, Dr. Eleazer, 1970-1975; 168534 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin, 1970-1975; 168533 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Bulletin Boards, 1964-1966; 168532 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Bulletin Proofs 1972-1973, 168531 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Bulletin-Type Information for Preregistration Purposes, 1973; 168530 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Bursar, 1964-1976; 168529 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Business Manager, 1963-1966; 168528 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Business Services Coordinator, 1967-1968; 168527 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Byrnes, Mr. Joseph A., 1974; 168526 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - College, Nature of, and its Deisrable Size, 1963; 168525 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - College of Business and Public Administration, 1972-1975; 168524 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Colleges, Private: Five Part Series, 1973; 168523 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Collegiate Institute, 1acker: Cooperative Arrangements, 1972; 168522 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Congress on Agriculture in the land of the Bible, 1976; 168521 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Garage: Proposed, undated; 168520 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - General Foods: Fellowships, 1961-1963; 168519 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Glee Club, 1968-1969; 168518 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Governmental Relations, 1967-1968; 168517 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Grace Internships, 1975; 168516 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Grading: Individual Problems, 1968-1971; 168515 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Graduate Courses for Undergraduates, 1965-1971; 168514 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - GSAS Fellowships, 1969-1972; 168512 (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - GSAS Deanship, 1964-1973; 168513 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - GSAS General File, 1970-1975; 168511 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - GSAS Policies, 1969-1971; 168510 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration: Newsletter, 1973; 168509 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Graduate Science School: Proposal, 1966-1974; 168508 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Graduate Social Work 1962-, 1962-1973; 168507 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226006 0
    - Graduate Work at the Heights, 1965-1967; 168506 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Graduates Taking Undergraduate Courses for Credit, 1970; 168505 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Grants, 1968-1974; 168504 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Great Teacher Awards, 1970-1973; 168503 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Greater New York Fund, 1968; 168502 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Guidance Associates, 1963-1965; 168501 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Gulbenkian Fellowships, 1965; 168500 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Mayerson, Dean Philip, 1971-1973; 168499 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Mayerson, Dean Philip, 1974-1975; 168498 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Mayerson, Dean Philip, 1976; 168497 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Mayerson, Dean Philip, 1977-1978; 168496 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Mayerson, Dean Philip: Alumni Association, 1973-1975; 168495 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Academic Planning: Reports and Correspondence, 1969-1978; 168494 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226007 8
    - Commission on Academic Planning: Minutes and Reports, 1976-1977; 168493 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Task Force on Undergraduate Admissions: Reports and Recommendations, 1976-1977; 168492 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Establishment of Banner and Shield, 1965-1973; 168491 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Chancellor Sidney Borowitz: Correspondence, 1972-1977; 168490 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - By laws: Reports, 1968-1973; 168489 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Faculty: Arthur M. Crosman, 1966-1972; 168488 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Faculty: Dean Paul Culley, 1966-1972; 168487 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Faculty: Dean David L. Hicks, 1967; 168486 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Faculty: Kenneth N. McKee, 1970-1973; 168485 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Faculty: Elsa E. Robinson, 1966-1973; 168484 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Faculty: Sidney Towne, 1966-1969; 168483 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Faculty: Anthony Zahareas, 1964-1971; 168482 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Prospective Vitae and Remarks, 1976-1977; 168481 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Institute of Fine Arts, 1958-1969; 168480 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Fire Drills, 1965-1967; 168479 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Flags: For Washington Square College, 1965-1968; 168478 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Ford Foundation: Accelerated Masters Program Printed Material, 1963-1974; 168477 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Foreign Student Statistics, 1973-1974; 168476 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Forensic Festival, 1967; 168475 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226008 6
    - Fort Bragg: Joint Program, 1962-1963; 168474 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Founders Day: Printed Material, 1967-1969; 168473 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Founders Day: Printed Material, 1969-1975; 168472 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - New York University in France: Printed Material, 1961-1978; 168471 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Freshmen: Summary and Reports, 1963-1966; 168470 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Freshmen Testing Program, 1961-1964; 168469 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Fulbright: Printed Material, 1965-1974; 168468 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Hall of Fame of New York University, 1973-1975; 168467 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Harbison Award: Printed Material, 1965-1972; 168466 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - John F. Hatchett: Printed Material, 1967-1968; 168465 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Charles Hayden Foundation for the Life Sciences, 1972; 168464 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Heights Campus: Proposed Study, 1967; 168463 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - HEW: Affirmative Action Worksheet, 1971; 168462 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - James M. Hester: Correspondence Printed Material, 1962-1967; 168461 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Hertz, 1971-1972; 168460 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226009 4
    - Higher Education Opportunity Program: Printed Material, 1968-1969; 168459 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - High School Students: Special Program, 1964-1966; 168458 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Homecoming Party: Printed Material, 1971-1975; 168457 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Honorary Degree: Nominations, 1968-1971; 168456 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Honors Studies on Man's Future, 1968-1969; 168455 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Housing at New York University, 1969-1973; 168454 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Meritorious Service Award, 1965-1971; 168453 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Public Affairs: Budget Review and Press Office, 1975-1976; 168452 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - William Von Raab: Correspondence, 1975-1979; 168451 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Tenure, 1968-1974; 168450 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Calendar: Academic Printed Material, 1968-1977; 168449 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson, 1973-1974; 168448 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Proposed Change to 4x4, 1977; 168447 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226010 2
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1975; 168446 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1975; 168445 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1976; 168444 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1976; 168443 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1976; 168442 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1976; 168441 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1976; 168440 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1976; 168439 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1977; 168438 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1977; 168437 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1977; 168436 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1977; 168435 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1977; 168434 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1977; 168433 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 168432 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Series II: Additional Dean's Files, 167548
  - Committee on Evening Programs, 1963-1969; 168421 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227095 2
  - Evening Students, 1963-1965; 168420 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Evening Studies, 1964-1968; 168419 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Examinations, 1964-1975; 168418 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Expense Cutting New Guidelines, 1972; 168417 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - External Investigations, 1969; 168416 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Misc. "F", 1965-1968; 168415 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Benefits, 1973; 168414 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Benefits Office (with retirement plan), 1971-1976; 168413 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Career Development, 1978; 168412 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Interdiscliplinary Faculty Colloquia, 1978; 168411 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council Newsletter, 1970-1979; 168410 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Faculty and Course Evaluation, 1967-1972; 168409 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Student Evaulation of Faculty, 1971-1973; 168408 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Student Evaluation of Faculty, 1975; 168407 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Grievance Procedures, 1970-1971; 168406 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1961; 168405 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Memo to FAS, 1971; 168404 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science at Washington Square, 1972-1975; 168403 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Opportunities, 1976-1978; 168402 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Personnel Action Procedures, 1974; 168401 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Release Time, 1978; 168400 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Relations, 1972-1976; 168399 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Union, 1970-1973; 168398 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Fales Collection/Lectureship, 1963-1968; 168397 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - FAS Chairman's Meeting, 1974-1976; 168396 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Deans Council / Agenda-Correspondence, 1969-1977; 223349
  - Federal Funding Outlook for Science, 1970; 168395 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Federal Register, 1979; 168394 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Federal Relations Office, 1976; 168393 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Vice Chancellor for Federal Relations, 1973-1974; 168392 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Federal Statutes, 1969; 168391 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Fees, 1963-1975; 168390 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Film Conference, 1969; 168389 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Vice President for Finance - Alan C. Claxton, 1976-1978; 168388 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Financial Aid Allocation, 1972-1975; 168387 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Dean of Financial Aid, 1967-1978; 168386 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Dean Mayerson Re: Financial Aid Meetings, 1976; 168385 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Financial Aid Renewal Policy, 1977; 168384 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1972-1977; 168383 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Fine Arts, 1968-1975; 168382 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Fiscal Review Group Report, 1975; 168380 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Foreign Students, 1963-1977; 168379 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Founders Committee of 100, 1963-1967; 168378 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Four Course Plan, 1967-1969; 168377 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - NYU in France Contract, 1969-1974; 168376 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - NYU in France GBA, 1969-1970; 168375 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - NYU in France General, 1969-1975; 168374 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - NYU in France ICCR, 1970; 168373 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - NYU in France Winders Trip, 1969; 168372 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - French, 1969-1975; 168371 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - French/Italian, 1968-1973; 168370 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227096 0
  - French: Review of Doctoral Program also German, Spanish and Portuguese, 1975; 168369 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising, 1968-1974; 168368 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Legal Alumni Fundraising R. Martin, 1975; 168367 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Physics Fundraising, 1973-1974; 168366 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising Ruder and Finn, 1972; 168365 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising - Sawhill, 1975; 168364 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - GSAS Committees, 1970-1973; 168363 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - GSAS Curriculum Committee, 1971-1975; 168362 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - GSAS Faculty Meetings, 1971-1973; 168361 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Gallatin Associates, 1963-1979; 168360 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Geology, 1967-1974; 168359 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - German, 1967/1975; 168358 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Deferred Gifts, 1972; 168357 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Gifts Statistics, 1974-1976; 168356 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Goals, 1963; 168355 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Goals Committee, 1973-1976; 168354 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Statewide Master Plan - Goals (NYU), 1972; 168353 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - The Goethe Institute, 1971-1976; 168352 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Goldin, 1967; 168351 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Good Will Ideas, 1971; 168350 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Governance, 1968-1969; 168349 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Senate Committee on the Standardization of Grades, 1971-1972; 168348 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Grade Survey Report, 1964-1965; 168347 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Grading System, 1962-1969; 168346 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Grading System, 1970-1977; 168345 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - GSAS General, 1968-1976; 168344 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Graduate Business Administration, 1970-1973; 168343 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Graduate International Study Program, 1976; 168342 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Grievance Committee, 1974-1976; 168341 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Heads and Chairmen 1968 to present, 1968-1978; 168340 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Health, Eduation and Welfare, 1972-1976; 168339 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Health and Health Related Courses, 1971-1979; 168338 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Health Services, 1964-1976; 168337 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Hebrew and Judaic Studies, 1963-1973; 168336 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Institute of Hebrew Studies, 1971-1972; 168335 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - High Lights, 1963; 168334 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - High School Information, 1973-1976; 168333 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Higher Education Act, 1965; 168332 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Higher Education Compact (Feasibility Study), 1971; 168331 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Higher Education Personnel Training Program, 1972-1973; 168330 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - History, 1968-975; 168329 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - History Graduate, 1969-1975; 168328 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Holiday Homecoming Party, 1971; 168327 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Holiday Homecoming, 1975; 168326 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Christmas Homecoming Party, 1969; 168325 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Honors Committee, 1976-1977; 168324 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Honors and Prizes, 1972; 168323 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Housing Office General, 1967-1974; 168322 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Spring '77 - Humanities Seminar Descriptions, 1977; 168321 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227097 8
  - IALAC - Ibero-American Language and Area Center, 1969-1973; 168320 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - IALAC Proposals, 1972-1975; 168319 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - ICSS, 1963-1964; 168318 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - In-house Candidates, 1980; 168317 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Institute of Afro-American Affairs, 1969-1974; 168316 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Doctor Minninberg - Office of Institutional Research, 1973-1975; 168315 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Institutional Research and Planning, 1967-1975; 168314 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Office of Institutional Research, 1969-1975; 168313 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Programs, 1969-1977; 168312 (Box 38, Folder 10)